What's it like being here? Obviously,
it's the first time you're going through
a change on this level. What's it like
being here for the first time and being
a part of this?
>> Yeah, I know. It's uh for sure exciting.
For for sure exciting. Uh just a great
opportunity, I think, for me and for
your shoe. Just uh yeah, just a great
opportunity. Yeah, it should be good.
>> What's the first time you got to
experience this process? Obviously, your
rookie deal took you to this point. How
was free agency for you? And then kind
of early in the tampering process, you
get to know where you're going.
>> Yeah, it was for sure like kind of
nerve-wracking for sure because you just
you just don't know what's going to
happen. But like uh I guess the only
thing different between being drafted
and being a free agent, like you get to
choose where you get to go and stuff. So
I think that's the only crazy thing, but
it was just a great opportunity that the
Cardinals were able to give. So it's
awesome.
>> Why choose the Cardinals?
>> She was just I think it's a really great
fit. Great fit. Great organization. I
think uh I think it should be really
good being able to pair with uh James
and should be should be really being
able to complement each other should be
awesome.
>> It seemed like you were one of the
priorities early on in the process.
You're one of the first names that came
out in this process. Uh did you sense
that you were feeling like a priority
with this team when you were starting to
have these negotiations?
>> Yeah, I felt like um I felt like it was
uh going to be really good really good.
I think my agent was in contact with
them once it all started. So I think um
shoot yeah they showed really like a lot
of interest. So shoot they believe in
me. Shoot I believe in I believe in
them. So it's uh shooting and now we're
here. So it should be as it was good.
>> Did they kind of explain to you what
they see as the plan with you and James
and Trey and kind of how that will will
work.
>> No I just think uh just the main the
main important or they haven't really
discussed that but more importantly just
the win. I think that's the main thing.
So being able to complement each other,
however the rotation or however that is
going to go, just being able to do what
we can to help this team win.
>> One thing is spotlight it was your
success running like outside zone. What
what do you think sets you up maybe with
that and also going into this this
scheme? What what sets you up for
success? How do you have so much success
running that type of style? Yeah, I
think uh it all came from running at
running at BYU, you know, the Y zone and
then being in Atlanta and then um shoot
with coach Lafler being from the Rams
being able to bring it back here and how
much success they had with the Rams
being able to bring it here. I think uh
I think it's really going to going to be
really successful. I think they're
bringing in all the pieces to to make it
really good. So, I think it should be
should be good. I think uh a lot of
excitement for this team, for this
offense, shoot for def Yeah, really for
for everything. So, it should be
awesome.
>> What uh what does
been on defense once upon a time. How
does that help you and and just how how
is that transition for you?
>> I think uh I think it for sure helps
just because of the scheme scheme wise
just knowing where defenders are going
to fit or where they should fit because
if there's an open gap then obviously
someone's wrong. So I think uh super
rare that um if a D lineman or D or a
linebacker is like doesn't have like
isn't in the right fit. So, I think uh
knowing that and then just switching
back, you're just like, "Damn, I'm
dialed now. I got it." So, it's uh it's
uh it's for sure it was for sure
different. I I enjoyed it. It was fun. I
think just being able to play freely,
trust your technique, but now just being
able to switch to the offensive side
just to continue just the ball.
>> Do you feel like that turned out to be
like a little bit of a cheat code for
you?
>> For sure. For sure. I think it was for
like like a lot of people said, "Oh,
like you were switching positions and
call it like, bro, like it was just it
was an opportunity to get on the field."
I think that was the most most important
thing for me. It's for sure little
Chi-Chi. I think uh it's for sure
underrated.
>> What did you learn playing with
John in Atlanta? He kind of takes to
kind of the committee setting that
you're going to have here.
>> Yeah, sure. I think shoot wait again.
>> What did you learn kind of playing with
and kind of you know sharing the back
deal with them? you kind of take to
implement here when you kind of have to
get into that role though of being like
a a committee type?
>> Yeah, I think uh really just feeding off
each other, you know, obviously he'll
like he'll make a big he'll make a big
play and then boom, okay, like I'll
mention to make a big play, but not
going crazy to where you're doing like
like crazy stuff like going cra like
like you're out of the technique and
stuff, but I think just uh just playing
your ball like don't chase for the big
play. The big play is going to happen.
just being able to she would just keep
going forward. Four and a half yards a
carry and then um yeah, she would just
keep moving the chains. I think that was
the big thing. So, being able to
compliment each other and um she would
just keep moving the chains and just end
of the end of the day getting the win. I
think that's always like to bring up the
ball security stat. Is that something
you like to talk about or is that
something maybe you're superstitious
about? like everyone everyone else likes
to talk about it more than me, but uh I
think uh yeah, obviously ball security
is job security is what my coach said.
So um being able to hold the ball high
and tight like it's like a it's the ball
is a lifeline. So being able to just
it's the fate of the organization. So
being able to just keep it off the
ground whether it's a pass or or
obviously when we're running the ball
just um keep it off the ground as much
as we can. Obviously, things are going
to happen like it could be a bad bounce
or a helmet, but uh just doing what we
can to not let that happen. So, I think
that's the most important thing. That's
just not for running backs, that's for
everyone who carries the ball.
>> For fans who who haven't seen you yet,
how would you describe your your running
style?
>> Um, pretty tough, pretty physical, I
would say. Um, yeah.
>> There are certain things you take the
most pride in.
not getting tackled by one guy. I think
falling forward, getting those uh
getting those yak yards, being able to
do that. I think I take a lot of pride
in that. Just not being like if it's a
one-on-one, just make sure we're going
forward, not getting stalmated uh for a
zero yard gain, whether it's uh if
there's a D lineman who breaks through
and he's free. Just being able to get
back at the line of scrimmage at least
instead of take a negative. I think
that's the biggest one.
>> Not a lot of changes, but big changes.
New coach, new quarterback coming in.
How does it feel to become part of the
next wave of Cardinals?
>> I think it's a it's a blessing, man. I
think it's a great opportunity for me,
great opportunity for the organization.
It's uh should be should be really
awesome. I'm excited for it, you know.
Just grateful that that we can get
trusted upon to be a part of this
organization. So,